<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Hobby Apps</title>
    <link>https://apps.joat.me/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Hobby Apps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 20:52:30 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://apps.joat.me/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About This Site</title>
      <link>https://apps.joat.me/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 16:43:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apps.joat.me/page/about/</guid>
      <description>This site documents my apps, written as hobby projects. All are open source and I don&amp;rsquo;t make money from them. The page also hosts my Privacy Policy, which is required for apps to be listed in most app stores.
Technical notes This website was built using Hugo with the Hyde theme, and is hosted by Github Pages
Site last updated 2023-08-27 11:31:32 -0400 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://apps.joat.me/page/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 10:00:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apps.joat.me/page/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My apps do not:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;collect personal data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;send data to me or to any third party&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;contain ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MPD Display</title>
      <link>https://apps.joat.me/page/mpd-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 20:52:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apps.joat.me/page/mpd-display/</guid>
      <description>This page describes version 0.3
Introduction Do you play your music collection or stream radio stations on the moOde audio player (or any other MPD-based music server)? Do you miss being able to see what&amp;rsquo;s playing on a display in your stereo rack without having to look at your phone? Do you have an unused Android tablet or phone gathering dust, or the budget to buy a cheap, entry-level tablet? Use MPD Display as a &amp;ldquo;now playing&amp;rdquo; screen, simpler and cheaper than building a Raspberry Pi with a built-in screen, much cheaper than a dedicated music streamer, more power-efficient than playing from your TV or computer, and more elegant than all of those options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Numbers Game Solver</title>
      <link>https://apps.joat.me/page/numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 19:59:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://apps.joat.me/page/numbers/</guid>
      <description>This page describes version 0.3.
The Numbers Game Solver finds solutions for the &amp;ldquo;Numbers&amp;rdquo; game (as played on long-running game shows in the UK, France and Australia). Note that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t let you play the numbers game, it just finds the best solutions.
Brief rules for the Numbers game:
Six &amp;ldquo;source&amp;rdquo; numbers are chosen from a pool of twenty-four. The pool contains two each of all the integers from 1 to 10, plus one each of 25, 50, 75 and 100.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
